对不起 你刚刚说是瑞秋吗
I'm sorry, did you just say it's Rachel?
对
Yes.
你喜欢瑞秋
Um, you like Rachel?
对 我喜欢瑞秋
Yes. I like Rachel.
瑞秋
Rachel?
对 听着 你知道的…
Yeah. Okay, but look, you know...
你知道我还喜欢谁吗 你
You know who else I like? You.
我应该要更常说 我喜欢你 罗斯
And it doesn't get said enough. I like you, Ross.
- 那个"瑞秋"    - 没什么大不了的
- "Rachel" Rachel?     - It's not a big deal.
没什么大不了的 抱歉 我只是…
It's not a big deal? I'm sorry, I just...
你刚刚说的那些话呢
What about the stuff you said?
你说你无法不去想她 你说你睡不着
How you can't stop thinking about her? How you can't sleep?
我是个演员 你知道吗
I'm an actor, you know?
演员习惯了夸张
As a group, we tend to be overdramatic.
怀着我孩子的瑞秋
Rachel-who's-carrying-my-baby Rachel?
我知道那很糟糕 我知道那是不对的 好吗
I know it's bad. And I know it's wrong, okay?
那是不可能会发生的事
It's not like anything's ever gonna happen.
那只是我的感觉 那会消失的
These are just feelings. They'll go away.
我得走了
You know, I gotta go.
罗斯
Hey, Ross...
我只是有个… 瑞秋
You know, I just have one... Rachel?
瑞秋
Rachel?
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
她在踢我
Oh, oh! Okay, she's kicking.
她在你的体内成长
She's growing inside you.
- 这一下踢得好用力   - 她是拒绝我最年轻的女孩
- That was a big one.     - That's the youngest girl to reject me.
- 大家好   - 嗨
- You guys!     - Hey there.
我要问你们 你们相信有心灵伴侣吗
Let me ask you. Do you believe in soul mates?
我相信
Oh, yes, I do.
每个人都有失落的另一半
There's one person out there for everyone.
你知道你该怎么找到他吗 停止再找了
You know how you find him? Stop looking.
我已经停止寻找罗素·克洛
I've stopped looking for Russell Crowe.
他会找到我的
He'll find me.
你呢
Uh-huh. And you?
不 我相信有些人非常适合彼此 但是…
No. I believe that, uh, certain people are more suited for each other, but...
- 心灵伴侣 我想他们并不存在   - 很好
- Soul mates? I don't think they exist.     - Good.
- 为什么    - 昨晚我遇到了摩妮卡的心灵伴侣
- Why?     - Well, last night, I met Monica's.
什么
What?
我跟这个男的约会 我发誓他是她的另一半
I had a date with this guy. I swear he's her other half.
你不觉得会有人比我更适合摩妮卡吧
You don't think there's somebody better suited for Monica than me?
他长什么样子
Well, what's he like?
- 他很高 是棕发   - 当然
- He's tall. He has brown hair.     - Of course.
一个发色跟我一样的高大男人 宇宙真的是太大了
A tall guy with hair similar to mine? Oh, unknowable universe!
- 他从事跟食物相关的行业   - 当然 他比较老吗
- He works with food.     - Oh, sure. Older?
- 没错 他是英国人   - 我正打算要问你
- Obviously. And he's British.     - I was just gonna ask!
他非常聪明 成熟有自信
Yeah? And he's so centered, and mature and confident.
真可惜他们彼此不认识
It's so sad they never met.
还好她老公没听到你那么说
Luckily, the guy she settled for can't hear you.
抱歉 或许我错了
Oh, I'm so sorry. Maybe I'm wrong.
我们会再约会 我会把他调查得更仔细
We're going out again. I'll find out more.
他跟别人是天生一对 你还要跟他约会
He's meant for her, and you're gonna date him?
或许他不是我的心灵伴侣 但我总得吃饭吧
He may not be my soul mate, but a girl's gotta eat.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
我刚跟乔伊谈过 我想知道你好不好
I talked to Joey. I wanted to see you.
我还是不敢相信 乔伊跟瑞秋
I still can't believe it. Joey and Rachel?
那像是你跟我在交往 只不过更奇怪
It's like you and me going out, only weirder.
我知道你很难过 我也想安慰你…
I know you're hurting...
但别再那么说了
...but don't say that again.
如果他们结婚了呢  他可能是我孩子的继父
What if they marry? He'd be the stepfather of my child.
你不必担心
You don't need to worry about.
他不会告诉她他的感觉
He'll never tell her how he feels.
就算他说了 你不知道她会有什么反应
If he did, you don't know how she'd react.
女人从来就不喜欢乔伊 我想他是个处男
Sure, women never like Joey. I think he's a virgin.
- 他不想追她   - 真的吗
- He isn't thinking about going for her.     - He's not?
他只想到你的感觉
All he's thinking about is how you're taking this.
这把他吓坏了 他想搬到佛蒙特去
It's freaking him out. He wants to move to Vermont.
- 为什么   - 他想离开这个国家
- Why?     - He wants to leave the country.
他认为你恨他
He thinks you hate him.
恨他
Hate him?
不 我不恨他
No, I don't hate him.
她是瑞秋 你知道吗
It's just, it's Rachel. You know?
我无法想像你有多难过…
I can't even imagine how hard this must be for you...
但我不希望你跟乔伊因此做不成朋友
...but I don't want you to lose Joey over it.
现在他得知道你还是他的朋友
Right now, he needs to know that you're still his friend.
好吧 我会跟他谈
Okay, I'll talk to him.
你最好快去
I'd do it soon.
他问我怎么把美金换成佛蒙特货币
He just asked me how to convert his dollars into Vermont money.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Oh, hi!     - Hi.
- 钱德 摩妮卡 他是唐   - 哈罗
- Chandler, Monica, this is Don.     - Hello.
- 哈罗 很高兴能认识你   - 你好吗
- Hello, nice to meet you.     - Nice to meet you.
心灵伴侣
Soul mate.
- 你们做了什么    - 我们在艾德瑞提卡吃午餐
- What are you guys doing?     - We had lunch at Adriatica.
- 番茄干是怎么了    - 对啊 现在是1985年吗
- What's with the sun-dried tomatoes?     - I know! Is this 1985?
- 我就是那么说的 这很奇怪吧   - 一点都不会
- That's what I said! Isn't it strange?     - Not really.
番茄干是怎么了
What's wrong with sun-dried tomatoes?
在烤鸡比萨上吗
On a barbecued-chicken pizza?
不是吗
No?
- 你喜欢哪家餐厅    - 奥克塔维欧 27与7
- What restaurants do you like?     - Octavio. 27-and-7.
- 还有亚利山多洛斯   - 天啊 我是那里的主厨
- There's this place, Alessandro's.     - Oh, my God! I'm the chef!
你是在开玩笑 你做的菜好吃极了
You're kidding! Your food is fantastic!
我要跟你谈谈你的菜单 有人要喝咖啡吗
I want to talk about your menu. Anyone want coffee?
我要喝拿铁 如果你要谈我的事 我跟你一起去
If you're talking about me, I'll go with you.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我发誓我不知道你们在这里
I swear, I didn't know you guys would be here.
反正你不相信心灵伴侣 所以…
You don't believe in soul mates, so...
我相信英俊的陌生人追我的老婆
I believe in handsome strangers who hit on my wife.
虽然我认为他们是心灵伴侣 那不代表会发生什么事
Just because I think they're soul mates doesn't mean anything'll happen.
- 菲比 做的好   - 哦
- Phoebe? Good work.     - Yeah?
他很棒 我爱他
He's great. I love him.
别担心 我们会帮你找到对象
Don't worry, we'll find you someone else.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
如果你是来打我的 我了解 这是我活该
I understand if you came by to hit me. I deserve it.
不 我不想打你
No, I don't want to hit you.
什么 你要踢我
What, then? Kick me?
不
No.
咬我
Bite me?
我不想对你怎么样
I don't want to do anything to you.
我只是要说 我没有生你的气…
I just want to say I'm not mad at you...
我当然也不恨你
...and that I certainly do not hate you.
我只是来告诉你
I just came here to say that.
等一下 罗斯
Hey, wait, Ross?
你想进来喝瓶啤酒吗
You wanna come in for a beer or something?
好吧
Yeah, sure.
你有啤酒吗
You got any beer?
我只有瑞秋留下香瓜饮料
All I got is melon stuff that Rachel left.
好吧
Okay.
你得了解一件事
You need to understand something.
我不会对瑞秋采取行动 好吧
I am never gonna act on this Rachel thing, okay?
我不会做出任何会危及你我友谊的事
I wouldn't do anything to jeopardize my friendship with you.
谢谢
Thank you.
总之 我只是…
Anyway, it'll just...
我得花点时间去遗忘
It'll take me a while to get over her.
我不确定我该怎么做 我没有陷入爱河过 所以…
I'm not sure how to do that. I've never been in love, so...
什么
What?
你爱上她了
You're in love with her?
- 对 我以为你知道   - 我不知道
- Yeah. I thought you knew that.     - Um, no.
听着 如果有帮助的话 我真的也不希望自己有那种感觉
Look, if it helps, I don't want to feel this way, honest.
我只是一直在想 "我得忘了这件事" 你知道吗
I just keep thinking, "I'll get over this," you know?
但我越这么想就越忘不了
But it just keeps getting harder.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do, you know?
我该怎么办
What do I do?
- 你得告诉她你的感觉   - 那一定是饮料害你这么说的
- You need to tell her how you feel.     - That's the green stuff talking.
我是认真的 你得知道她的感觉
I'm serious. You need to find out where she is.
如果她不喜欢你 你可以继续往前走
If she's not where you are, you can start to move on.
但如果 我不是说她会…
But what if, and I'm not saying she will be...
如果她喜欢你…
If she is where you are...
我的尴尬感觉不该妨碍你们
...then my feeling weird shouldn't stand in the way.
- 你确定    - 对
- Are you sure?     - Yeah.
如果她会跟别的男人在一起…
If she ends up with somebody else...
说真的 她找不到更好的人选
...the truth is, she couldn't find a better guy.
谢谢
Hey, thanks.
- 你什么时候要跟她谈    - 天啊 我得跟她谈
- So when are you gonna talk to her?     - Oh, my God. I have to tell her.
我还没有想过 我该说什么
I haven't thought about it. What should I say?
我能体谅你 但我们别太过分了
I'm understanding, but let's not get carried away.
好的 对不起
Right, sorry. Sorry.
我该说什么
What am I gonna say?
很难喝吧
Yeah, tell me about it.
我解决了进口酒的问题 现在全力研究起司
I'm phasing out the wine importing and focusing more on the, um, cheese.
你说起司吗
Cheese, you say?
就是那种臭臭的东西 唐
That's some pretty smelly work, huh, Don?
- 对不起   - 起司很臭
- Excuse me?     - Cheese. It's smelly.
你一定也常常闻起来很臭
You must smell a lot of the time too.
不会的 但我觉得起司越臭越好
Uh, not really. But with cheese, I think the smellier, the better.
我也是 钱德讨厌它 在家我不能吃蓝起司
Me too! Chandler hates it. I can't have blue cheese in the house.
你还是嫁给了他
And you're still married to him?
我想到法国只吃面包跟起司
I would like to go to France and eat nothing but bread and cheese.
甚至不要面包 只要起司
Not even bread. Just cheese.
不 我要面包
No, I want the bread.
还有馅饼
And pastries.
跟小馅饼
And pate.
我不是真的兴奋 只是以前我很胖
I'm really not high. I just used to be fat.
我在罗亚尔谷有栋别墅 你可以住在那里
I have a villa in the Loire Valley you can stay in.
那是用起司做的吗
Is it made of cheese?
不 用起司做的房子 那很不可思议吧
No. A house made of cheese, wouldn't that be great?
- 我明天就想搬进去   - 少来了
- I'd move in tomorrow!     - Oh, come on!
- 你听到了吗    - 对不起
- Listen to this!     - I'm so sorry.
- 我们该怎么办    - 他们都要起司屋
- What do we do?     - They both want a house of cheese.
我不知道你该怎么办
I don't know how you fight that.
好吧 我可以做到 我可以告诉她我的感觉
Okay, okay. I can do this. I can tell her how I feel.
好吧 挺直腰杆
Okay, stand up straight.
深呼吸一下
Take a couple deep breaths.
表现出自信
Look confident.
乔伊 怎么了
Joey? What's up?
我来找你 因为我想告诉你一件事
I came by because I want to talk to you about something.
怎么了
What's up?
就在走廊上谈 我们是动物吗
Here, in the hall? What are we, animals?
我开会要迟到了 你能快点说吗
I'm late for a meeting. Could you make it quick?
我是来告诉你…
I just came by to tell you that...
我想跟你一起吃晚餐
...I want to have dinner with you.
- 没问题 告诉我到哪里找你   - 好吧
- Sure. Just tell me where to meet you.     - Okay.
好吧 太棒了
Okay. That's good.
这给你几小时的时间做好准备
That gives you a couple of hours to prepare.
你们从来不敲门吗
Don't you people ever knock?
我想请唐跟菲比过来 很棒吧
I'd like to have Don and Phoebe over.
没问题 你去安排吧
Sure. Set it up.
我去看征友广告
I'll just be browsing through the personals.
你没事吧 你有点怪怪的
Are you okay? You're acting weird.
很好
Yeah. Fine.
我不完美
Not perfect.
但我够好了
But good enough.
天啊 你是怎么了
Jeez, what's with you?
抱歉 你刚刚说"起司"吗
I'm sorry, did you say "cheese"?
- 怎么了    - 菲比说你跟唐是心灵伴侣
- What's going on?     - Phoebe says you and Don are soul mates.
我是不相信 但你们两个处得很好
I don't believe in that, but you two get along.
如果你想跟唐住在起司屋 我可以退出
I'll step aside if you wanna go with Don and live in a house of cheese.
- 你不相信心灵伴侣  - 对 但我相信"番茄干先生"信
- You don't believe in soul mates?     - No, but I'm sure "tomatoes" does.
我也不相信心灵伴侣
I don't believe in soul mates, either.
- 你不相信    - 对
- You don't?     - Nope.
我们不是注定要在一起的
We weren't destined to end up together.
我们陷入爱河 努力经营我们的关系
We fell in love and work hard at our relationship.
有时候我们非常努力
Some days we work really hard.
你不想跟唐住在起司屋
So you don't want to live with Don in a cheese house?
不 我想了一下 你知道它打扫起来有多辛苦吗
No, I've had second thoughts. Do you know how hard it'd be to clean?
- 我爱你   - 我知道
- I love you.     - I know.
我要带你去吃晚餐
I'm gonna take you out to dinner.
我找到一个做起司条和墨西哥辣椒卷最好吃的地方
I found this place that makes the greatest mozzarella sticks and jalapeno poppers.
不要吗 那真的很好吃
No? They taste so good.
我知道钱德是在开玩笑 但是他一摸我的肚子就会这样
It happens whenever Chandler touches my stomach.
我担心宝宝不喜欢他
I'm worried the baby won't like him.
- 你没事吧    - 没事
- Are you okay?     - Yeah, sure.
听着 我…
Uh, look, the reason...
这里很热吗
Is it hot in here?
不会 我不觉得 你为什么不把毛衣脱掉
No, not for me. Why don't you take off your sweater?
这个地方不错…
This is a nice place...
我的T恤印了卡尔文上荷比丝的样子
...and my T-shirt has a picture of Calvin doing Hobbes.
天啊 真的吗 我能看一下吗
Oh, my God, really? Can I see it?
当然可以
Yeah, sure.
我想荷比丝不会太喜欢
I wouldn't think Hobbes would like that so much.
我们认识多久了
How long have we known each other?
七 八…
Um, seven, eight...
八年了
Eight years. Wow.
- 真的很久了   - 对
- Uh-huh. A long time.     - Yeah.
但过去几星期以来 我…
But over the past few weeks, I...
好吧 抱歉让你们久等 今天客人真的很多
Okay! Sorry about the wait, but it is mega-jammed in here.
今晚的特餐是…
Our specials tonight...
- 你能等一下再来吗    - 好吧
- Could you give us a second?     - Sure.
时间到
Second's up!
你们不是那种客人
Not that kind of table.
你要说什么
So you were saying?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
你问我们认识了多久 我说八年
You asked how long we knew each other, and I said eight years.
后来服务生走过来 害他少了一半的小费…
Then the waiter came over and cut his tip in half...
我们说到那里了
...and now here we are.
没错
Yeah. Here we are.
我想我爱上你了
I think I'm falling in love with you.
什么
What?
我爱上你了
I'm falling in love with you.
你在跟谁说话
Who are you talking to?
你在开玩笑 这是闹着玩的
Oh, you're kidding. It's a joke.
真的很好笑
Funny. It's funny!
我不了解
I don't get it.
好吧
Okay.
哇
Wow.
你…
Are you, um?
怎么会…
How did, um?
什么时候
When?
那真的重要吗
Does it really matter?
哇
Wow. Wow.
这里好热
It is hot in here.
我知道这真的很令人吃惊
I know this is a lot.
你什么都不必说
You don't have to say anything.
你要花多少时问思考都可以
You take as much time as you need.
好吧 你得说说话
Okay, you gotta say something.
乔伊 我非常爱你
Joey, I love you so much.
- 但是…   - 但是
- But...     - But.
乔伊
Joey?
对 那是…
Right. Hey, that's, uh...
没关系 真的
That's okay. That's fine.
我料到你会这样
It's, uh, pretty much what I was expecting.
那没什么大不了的 好吗
It's no big deal, all right?
- 我想我得走了   - 请不要这样离开
- I think I'm gonna go.     - Please don't leave like this.
你不能这样对一个孕妇
You can't do this to a pregnant woman!
别那么做
Don't start doing that.
你不能那么做 因为你把我弄哭了…
You can't do that, because you're gonna make me...
我们一起哭吧
Oh, there we go!
- 可以吗    - 没问题
- Can I?     - Sure.
乔伊 我不想失去…
Oh, Joey. I don't want to lose...
嘿
Hey, hey.
你不会的 好吗 永远不会
You can't, okay? Ever.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
请你不要那么说
Please don't be sorry.
好吧 别感到抱歉
Okay? Don't be sorry.
我只是在开玩笑
You know, I was only kidding.
对 那真的很好笑
Yeah, that was a real good one.
- 他们是你的客人    - 对
- Is this your table?     - Yeah.
- 你得在这里待上一整晚   - 我知道
- You'll be here all night.     - I know.
我连特餐内容都还没有说
I haven't even read the specials.
他们怎么了
What's the matter?
我不知道 我想或许他们之中有人快死了
I don't know. I think maybe one of them is dying.
我希望是那个女的
I kind of hope it's the girl.
那个男的真的很帅
The guy is really cute!